Oluyemisi Soetan CPM,CSPO

Project Manager

Contact

Phone +2348030880766

E-mail

soetanoluyemisi@gmail.co m

Skills

PLC Management

Excellent

Agile methodology

Very Good

Vendor Management

Very Good

Risk Assessment

Very Good

Project Planning Tools

Very Good

Stakeholder Management

Very Good

Monitoring and Evaluation

Very Good

Change Management

Very Good

Diligent CSPO and CPM certified Project Manager offering 5 years of success in product roadmap development, market research and data analysis. Highly skilled in identifying opportunities to maximize revenue. Driven and strategic with proven history of superior market penetration and product launch.

Work History

2022-02 -Current

SeniorProject Manager

Zojatech.

- Oversaw entire product deployments of four products, through the life-cycle within time and budget.
- Developed project plans including scope, cost, timeline and deliverables.
- Coordinate internal resources and third parties/vendors for the flawless execution of projects.
- Tracked project performance, specifically to analyze the successful completion of short and long-term goals.
- Managed changes to the project scope, project schedule, and project costs using appropriate verification techniques.
- Perform risk management to minimize project risks.
- Established and maintained relationships with third parties/vendors.
- Created and maintained comprehensive project documentation.

2020-09 -2022-01

Project Manager

Sendbox Technologies

- Coordinate internal resources and third parties/vendors for the flawless execution of projects.
- Tracked project performance, specifically to analyze the successful completion of short and long-term goals.
- Managed changes to the project scope, project schedule, and project costs using appropriate verification techniques.
- Created and maintained comprehensive project documentation.

2019-01 2020 - 08

Digital Marketing Associate.

Korak Healthcare.

- Developed and implemented digital marketing strategies to increase brand awareness and drive traffic to the company's website or social media platforms.
- Created and managed online advertising campaigns across various channels, such as Google Ads, Facebook Ads, and LinkedIn Ads.
- Monitored and analyzed the performance of digital marketing campaigns using tools like Google Analytics or social media

- analytics platforms.
- Managed the social media accounts, including creating content, scheduling posts, and engaging with followers.

2017-11 -2018-12

Social Media Officer

Awesome Fresh, Lagos

- Managed and updated the organization's social media profiles and pages.
- Created engaging content for various social media platforms, including text posts, images, videos, and infographics.
- Planned and scheduled social media posts using social media management tools to maintain a consistent posting schedule.

Education

2011-02 -	Bachelor of Science :
2016-09	Physiotherapy

Obafemi Awolowo University - Ile Ife

2022-09 -	Certified Product Manager:
2023-02	Product Management

AIPMM - Online

2022-07 -	PLG Expert :	Product	Led	Growth
-----------	---------------------	---------	-----	--------

2022-08 Product School - Online

2022-06 - Business Strategy And Innovation: Strategy

University of Pennsylvania - Coursera

2024-02 - Software Product Management

2024-05 University of Alberta - Coursera

Certifications

02 -2023	AIPMM - CPM - Certified Product

Manager.

04-2024 Scrum Alliance - CSPO - Certified Scrum

Product Owner.

